我们这里有内奸  兄弟
We got a rat in here, bro.
我要你时刻关注博伊特的电话  邮件
I need you to stay on top of Voight's phone calls, emails,
行踪  一切消息
his whereabouts, everything.
-查理是谁  -我原来和他一起鬼混
- So who's Charlie? - He's a guy I used to run with.
还是说你从他身边逃跑了
Run with or run from?
-带他走  -我们可说好了的
- I want him out of here. - We had a deal!
我一向言而有信
I keep my word.
有警员遇袭  看见什么了吗
We got officers down! You see anything?
呼叫总部  警员中枪了
10-1, squad! Officer shot.
亚德勒斯·迪亚斯因几项与毒品有关的谋杀案获罪
Adres Dias convicted of several drug-related murders...
他不会有事的
He's gonna be okay.
-知道吗  -谢谢
- All right? - Thank you.
医生出来了
Look.
道森太太
Mrs. Dawson.
他不会有事吧
Is he gonna be all right?
我们会密切观察
We're gonna monitor him closely,
但可能还需要再进行一次手术
but he may need a second surgery.
他现在还没脱离危险
He's not out of the woods yet.
-我能见他吗  -当然可以
- Can I see him? - Of course.
这里
Right here.
安东尼奥
Antonio.
亲爱的
Hey, baby.
Hi, honey.
兄弟
Hey, big guy.
拜尔登怎么样
Belden?
走了
Gone.
那两个警卫呢
Those guards?
都死了
Both dead.
找到他
Find him.
一定会的
We will.
爸爸不会死对吧
Dad's gonna live, right?
他不会有事的对吧
He's gonna be okay?
当然了
Absolutely.
他不会有事的
He's gonna be fine.
我跟你差不多大时
You know, when I was your age,
我父亲也来住过院
my father was in this very same hospital.
你爸爸是我认识的最厉害的警察之一
Your dad is one of the toughest cops I know.
他出院时一定会更健康更强壮
He's gonna walk out of here stronger than ever.
听着  你们俩留下照顾劳拉和孩子
Listen, you two stay here with Laura and the kids.
不要让他们离开你们的视线  明白吗
They don't leave your sight. You hear me?
明白
Yes, sir.
警长  恕我直言
Sarge, no disrespect.
我更想跟你一起去抓八爪
I'd rather be out there hunting down Pulpo.
难道还有什么
What is more important
比保护安东尼奥和他的家人更重要吗
than protecting Antonio and his family?
复制文件
你是迷路了吗
Are you lost?
据我所知  这可是你上司的办公桌
Last time I checked, this was your boss's desk.
我在给情报组成员安装新的
I'm installing new incident-reporting software
事故报告软件
on all of the intelligence computers.
你这里搞定后
Well, when you're finished here,
能去楼下帮忙看看吗  我的电脑死机了
will you come down and fix mine? It froze up.
没问题
Of course.
我马上下去
I'll be right down.
文件复制中
下载完毕
艾琳
Erin.
是你啊  安妮
Hey. Oh, Annie.
-很高兴见到你  -我也是
- Good to see you. - You too.
不好意思
Um, I'm sorry.
我一个同事中枪了  我一直在医院
One of my partners got shot, and I've been at the hospital,
应该发短信给你的
and I should have texted you.
没事
Oh, no, it's all right.
我有麻烦了吗
Am I in trouble?
不  不是不是
No. No, no, no.
怎么会呢
Not at all.
小家伙
Hey, bud.
你要跟我打招呼吗
You gonna come say hi to me?
-艾琳  你好  -怎么了
- Hey, Erin. - What?
这是怎么回事  长得真快啊
What is going on with you? Are you sprouting?
什么时候这么高了
When did you get so tall?
让我单独跟你妈妈说几句好吗
You give me and your mom a minute?
好
Okay.
抱歉让你大老远跑来
Listen, I'm sorry I made you come all the way here.
我是想当面跟你说
I just wanted to tell you in person.
查理回来了
Charlie's back.
他回来干什么
Why is he back?
我也不清楚  但他问起过你
I don't know, but he asked about you.
你跟他说特拉维斯的事了吗
Did you tell him about Travis?
当然没有
Of course not.
但他已经来了  所以你想怎么办
But he's here, so how do you want to play this?
我可以让他不要去招惹你
I can tell him to leave you alone,
也可以把你的号码给他
or I can give him your phone number,
也可以找个地方一起好好谈谈
or I can pick a place for all of us to meet,
我也会去的
and I can be there.
我希望你也到场
Yeah, I want you to be there.
好
Okay.
好  我会安排的
Okay, I'll set it up.
谢谢
Thanks.
大家听好了
Listen up.
八爪的所作所为
What Pulpo did downstairs
是对我们大家庭的攻击
was an attack on our family.
先是威尔海特  现在是安东尼奥
First Willhite and now Antonio.
所以我把话说清楚了
So let me be clear.
别管什么逮捕令  别管那些纪律
Forget warrants. Forget the rules.
我们要不惜一切代价抓他归案
It's on us to catch him.
抓到他以后
And when we do,
必须把他交到我和埃尔文手里
he's to be handed off to me and Alvin.
他们刚在区内发现了可疑车辆
They found a possible getaway vehicle up on division.
有八爪的行踪吗
Any sign of Pulpo?
只发现了一具男性尸体
One dead male.
还没确认尸体身份
No confirmation on the body yet.
-我们走  -警长
- Let's go. - Hey, Sarge.
我只是想确认一下
I'm just looking for a little clarification
你刚才那些话的意思
on what you just said.
八爪不会活着回监狱
Pulpo ain't making it back to a jail cell.
这么说够清楚了吗
That clear enough for you?
谢谢
Thanks.
-查到些什么  -全是假的
- Well, what do you got? - All fake.
他们找了一辆普通的面包车  贴上花纹
They took a regular van and put the decals on it,
假装成囚车的样子
so it looks like a paddy wagon.
八爪从运送他的囚车里逃出来
The prison transport van that Pulpo escaped in
那辆囚车在六个街区外被发现
was found six blocks from the district.
他把车丢在那  然后换了这辆车
He ditched it, and he switched to this.
尸体在哪里
Where's the body?
这里
Over here.
司机戴着商厦保安的徽章
Driver's wearing a mall security badge
应该是从军需用品店买的
someone bought at an army surplus store.
法医通过指纹确认了身份
Forensics I.D.'d the prints.
他的名字叫卡洛斯·格瓦拉
His name's Carlos Guvera.
是哥伦比亚贩毒集团的毒贩
He's a known bagman for the Colombian cartel.
难怪八爪不会留活口
Oh, and Pulpo couldn't let the guy live to talk.
大家看  八爪的女友和儿子也曾和他一起在车上
Hey, guys, Pulpo's girlfriend and son were with him.
你们猜他会不会带着一家子
How much you want a bet he's taking his family unit
逃回哥伦比亚去了
and hightailing it back to Colombia?
我们已经把他的名字和照片
We got his name and his mug shot
发到了所有边防检查站
at every border checkpoint.
火车站和机场
Train stations, airports.
如果这都是八爪事先精心安排的
If Pulpo planned this far,
他肯定已经做好了逃脱方案
you better believe he planned for a way to get out.
有什么有价值的信息吗
What do you have for me?
有
Yeah.
我下载了他电脑里所有的档案和电邮
I was able to download all those reports and emails.
你以为博伊特会把自己的罪证
Do you think that Voight is gonna leave any real dirt
存在电脑里叫"腐败"的文件夹里吗
on his computer under a file labeled "corruption"?
吉恩  我要监控他的网络
Jin, I need a wire on his nextel,
在他的手机和车里装窃听器
his personal phone, and inside his car.
我正在想办法
Listen, I'm planning
很快就会加大对他的监控范围
on ramping up surveillance on him soon.
想办法
Planning on it?
如果你这周内还找不到有用的线索
If you don't give me something that I can use by next week,
我向你保证联调局会
I'm going to make sure that your father
立刻找上你的父亲
gets a visit from the FBI.
-别以为你了解...  -我确实了解
- Don't think you understand-- - I absolutely understand.
-不  -我赞同你的想法
- No. - I agree with you.
我们真要为了博伊特违反纪律吗
So we're all willing to just go off book for Voight?
我才从警校毕业四个月  兄弟
Look, I'm four months out of the academy, man.
我只是按上头的命令行事
I just do what I'm told.
就算是命令你动用私刑也照做吗
Even if that means being part of a lynch mob?
我会调转枪头违抗命令吗
If you're asking if I'm gonna turn over my shield
不  我不会
and protest, no, I'm not.
你会吗
Are you? I mean--
我是想说  我们该怎么办
What I'm saying is, what do we do?
如果找到八爪  真要把他交给博伊特吗
If we find Pulpo, are we just gonna turn him over to Voight?
好了  大家别紧张
All right, everybody relax.
等我们抓到八爪  再想怎么办吧
What we do is find Pulpo, and then we can figure it out.
是的  这正是我们需要的
Yeah, that's exactly what we needed, yeah.
琳娜家有什么线索吗
Anything at Lina's house?
司法官检查过了  一无所获
Marshals stormed it. Came up empty.
琳娜的家人呢
What about Lina's family?
她妈妈住在南边
Her Mom's got a place on the South side,
没有前科  电话通信记录也正常
came up clean, and so did her cell phone records,
不过我觉得还是应该去拜访一下
but I think it's worth a drive-by.
好的  带个人一起去
Good. Take someone and go do it.
他杀了最后一个忠于他的人
So last guy loyal to him, he kills.
没有朋友  没有亲人
No friends, no family.
你们还查到些什么
Who else do you have?
八爪的律师
What about Pulpo's lawyer,
安东尼·提姆珀呢
Anthony Timpone?
提姆珀
Timpone.
他是市里半数的罪犯的律师
He reps half the criminals in the city.
这么说吧  如果不是警方要求
He didn't get that rep by cooperating with the police,
他绝不会合作
I'll tell you that.
我有办法
I got an idea.
我父母离婚的时候
When my parents got divorced,
我妈找了个人打电话去我爸公司恐吓他
my Ma had this guy call in a threat to my Dad's office.
好几个月他都担惊受怕地检查车底有没有炸弹
He was checking for bombs underneath his car for months.
警长
Sergeant.
现在当值的人里有会说西班牙语的吗
Hey, you got a Spanish speaker on shift?
加西亚  把你手头那些破事交给安德鲁斯
Hey, Garcia, play pass-the-bum to Andrews,
然后过来
and get your ass over here.
-怎么了  -伙计
- What's up? - Hey, man.
我需要你打电话威胁个人
I need you to call in a death threat.
行吗  过来
All right? Come on.
你永远不知道何时有机会发光
You never know when it's your time to shine.
快去
Go.
那个律师死定了
El abogado es un hombre muerto.
听清楚了吗
Lo entiendes?
提姆珀死定了
Timpone esta muerto.
我们来了
Estamos llegando.
这样够可信吗
That convincing enough?
我就会信
I bought it.
-等等  -放松点
- Hey, wait. - Easy, easy.
芝加哥警署  大块头
C.P.D., big guy.
等等  等等
Wait. Wait!
你们不能进去
You can't go in there.
怎么回事
What the hell?
你把枪拿出来干什么  提姆珀
Ooh, what's with the hardware, Timpone?
-我有持枪许可  -我们在找八爪
- I have a permit. - We're looking for Pulpo.
很显然  他也在找我
Yeah, apparently, he's looking for me.
我刚接到他打来的电话
I just got a call from him.
你怎么看
What do you make of that?
八爪打来的电话
A call from Pulpo?
不是什么好事
That ain't good.
你收费可不便宜
But you don't come cheap.
怎么回事
So what happened?
八爪把最后一笔钱花在了你身上
Pulpo spend his last chunk of change on you?
你救了他的命  现在他想退款了
You got life, now he wants a refund?
对  所以我才雇了个保镖
Yeah, that's why I got him.
你觉得他要是真想来
You think that you and some rent-a-cop
就凭你和一个业余警察
are gonna keep him from getting in here
阻止得了他吗
if he really wanted to?
我抓过很多人渣
I've arrested a lot of scumbags
后来都被你放走了
you've put back out on the street,
所以我得老实告诉你
so I got to be honest with you.
我根本不在乎你会怎么样
I don't give a damn what happens to you,
不过如果你有线索能帮我找到八爪
but if you got anything that can help me find Pulpo,
对我们双方都好
it might be good for both of us.
八爪受审时
During Pulpo's trial,
曾问过我在哪可以买到新身份
he asked where he could buy sets of new identities,
要最高级的伪装文件
top-of-the-line papers.
我就把他介绍给了我以前的客户
So I referred him to an old client of mine.
叫什么名字
What's his name?
尼尔·邦克  他是个公证员
Neil Bunker-- he's a notary public.
在北克拉克有个照相馆
He's got a camera joint on North Clark.
邦克因为各种原因被逮捕过
Bunker's been arrested for everything
从伪造护照到仿制黄牛票
from bogus passports to counterfeit bulls tickets.
我们去看看八爪有没有留下什么蛛丝马迹
So let's see if Pulpo's left any bread crumbs.
照相
相片杂货
你们好
Hey there.
欢迎光临
Welcome.
警官
Officers.
有什么能帮你们的吗
How can I help you?
认识他吗
Recognize him?
不认识
No.
你确定
You sure?
别管他
Don't worry about him.
我们听说如果有人想要无不良记录的
We heard if someone's looking for clean I.D.s
身份证和信用卡  就会来找你
and credit cards, they come to you.
如果你想洗照片  欢迎
You want to get some pictures developed, great.
除此之外...
But otherwise--
你确定你不认识他吗
You sure you don'recoize him?
-不认识  -真不认识
- No. - No?
不认识
No.
你开的是什么店
What kind of shop are you running here?
就是照相馆  拍照片什么的
It's just a photo shop. That's what we do--photos.
-真没什么  -把他带过来
- I don't know what to tell you. - Bring him back here.
过来
Come on.
这地方是干什么的
So what's is little operation?
不...我...这个...
No, I-- no, I--this--
看来有人剪过头发了
Looks like somebody got a haircut.
找到八爪了
Got Pulpo.
好  我再问一次
Okay, let's start over.
八爪在哪儿
Where's Pulpo?
我知道他是什么人
I know who he is.
我不想让他找我麻烦
I'm not having him come after me.
你们还是把我抓走吧
You're gonna have to arrest me.
谁说要抓你了
Who said anything about arrest?
我只知道
I mean, all I know is,
你冲警察开枪了
you took a shot at a police officer.
什么
What?
捡起来
Pick it up.
捡起来  快啊  捡起来
Pick it up. Go ahead, pick it up.
别看我
Don't look at me.
你有两个选择
Listen, you have two choices.
你可以朝我们开枪然后逃走
You can shoot your way out of here,
要不然就告诉我八爪的事
or you can tell me about Pulpo.
我给他做了三张身份证
I made him three sets of I.D.s
还有几张与假证名字相符的信用卡
and a couple of credit cards to match.
-他带着一对母女吗  -没错
- Was he with a woman and a kid? - Yes.
你知道他们去哪儿了吗
And you have no idea where they're going?
-不知道  -说得跟真的似的
- No. - Yeah, of course not.
真不知道  我发誓
No, I swear.
把他带回局里
Hey, take him in.
-起诉他  -明白
- Book him. - Yeah.
起诉他教唆罪
Aiding and abetting.
但我都招了啊
But I talked.
招得不够快
Not fast enough.
监控上有线索吗
Anything off the P.O.D.s?
没有  但芝加哥城里所有摄像头
No, but I've got every electric eye
我都在密切监控了
in the city wide open.
萨姆纳的事怎么样了
What about the Sumner thing?
什么意思
What about it?
我让你去查查她
I told you to look into her.
你在跟我犯傻吗
You getting stupid on me?
没有
Uh, no. No.
当然记得
Yeah.
给你
Here.
她上周的通话记录都在这里
I pulled all her calls in the last week.
有打给内务部的电话吗
Any with Internal Affairs?
她给那里一个叫埃德文·史迪威的人
Um, I think she made three calls over there
打了三个电话
to a Edwin Stillwell.
但我不知道他们通话的目的
I don't know what they're about, though.
她有可能只是有个案子没破要咨询
I mean, she might have a case pending.
伯吉斯在哪里
Where's Burgess?
-去洗手间了  -补妆  对吧
- Went to the bathroom. - Fixing her makeup, huh?
-或许吧  -他怎么样了
- Maybe. - How's he doing?
休息中  他是个战士
Resting. He's a fighter.
有小套餐哦
Combos.
太感谢你了
Hi. Thanks so much.
孩子们可爱吃了
The kids love those.
小事一桩  你怎么样了
No biggie. How you doing?
-还在撑着  -很好
- Hanging in there. - Good.
谢谢
Thanks.
我和你们爸爸认识很久了
You know, I've known your dad a long time.
他刚来警署时  我们被分在
We were on the same patrol unit
同一支巡逻队里
back when he was a rookie.
我们有一次执行任务
And we went on this call one time,
把一名毒贩子追到了一座危房里
chased this dealer into a crack house.
他隔着门拿着一把霰弹枪打我们
He shot at us through the door with a 12-gauge.
他打中了我的屁股  我倒下了
I got hit in the hip and went down.
这个坏人本可以把我了结了
And this bad guy, he would have finished me off,
但你爸爸  他跑过来救了我
but your dad, he ran over and picked me up.
他把你背走了吗
He carried you?
没错
He did.
我以前没这么胖
I was a little thinner back then.
他们把散弹从我身上拔出
So they plucked the buckshot out of me,
把我藏到一张桌子后面
and they stuck me behind a desk.
要不是多亏了你们老爸...
But if it wasn't for your dad...
好吧  随时告诉我们进展  谢谢
All right, keep us posted. Thanks.
琳娜妈妈家那边有动静了吗
Anything on Lina's mom's house?
没有  但我安排了几个卧底
No, zip, but I've got a couple of undercovers
在街上停车盯着
parked down the street.
在医院里
At the hospital--
我从没听博伊特讲过他父亲的事
I've never heard Voight talk about his father.
到底是怎么一回事
What's the whole story?
《芝加哥太阳报》都有刊登过
Nothing you can't find in the Sun-Times archives.
你不是跟他一起住过吗
You lived with him.
我只知道
Look, all I know
每次城里有警察中弹
is that every time a cop gets shot in this city,
他就会变成那个样子
Voight gets that same look in his eye.
我出去透透气
I need some air.
每天都自愿来到警局
Must feel strange going to a police station
感觉一定很奇怪吧
every day voluntarily.
直说吧
I got to make this quick.
博伊特现在怎么样了
Hey, what ever happened to Voight?
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
死了还是在牢里
Dead or in jail.
事实上  他是我的上司
Actually, he's my boss.
你的上司
Your boss.
警署里的吗
Up in here?
没错
That's right.
不错
Classic.
真不错
That's classic.
你跟他说让他离我远点
Okay, well, you can tell him to leave me alone.
告诉他我被迫夹着尾巴做人
Tell him I got flushed down the toilet,
就为了让你当警察  记得吗
so you could play cop. Ring a bell?
你什么都不知道
You don't even know.
听着  你有个儿子  查理
Listen, you got a son, Charlie,
安妮生的
with Annie.
他叫特拉维斯
His name's Travis,
他在你走后六个月出生的
and he was born six months after you left.
什么
What?
为什么没有人告诉我
How come no one told me?
没人联系得上你
No one could get a hold of you.
我会定个时间大家一起见一面
I'm gonna set up a time for us all to meet.
再联系
I'll be in touch.
我们有线索了
Okay. We've got a hit.
琳娜的假名  玛丽亚·埃斯波西托
Lina's fake I.D., Maria Esposito,
20分钟前刚刚用她的假信用卡
was just used along with her fake credit card
从中途机场租了一辆车
to rent a vehicle from Midway 20 minutes ago.
-发现她们的行踪了吗  -比那更好
- Get eyes on 'em? - Even better.
车上有卫星定位系统
It's got a GPS tracker on it.
我们有车的准确位置
Got its exact location.
正在沿普拉斯基街往北开
Heading north on Pulaski.
太好了
Beautiful.
萨姆纳  你不用去了
Sumner, you're out.
好  我留下来监控...
Oh, okay, I'll stay back and watch the--
你不用留在这个部门了
No, you're out of my unit.
你被调走了
You're transferred.
从明天开始你去缉毒队工作
As of tomorrow, you work in narcotics.
你不能把我调走
You can't transfer me.
我已经打过电话了
I already made the call.
你这样做不对
You're making a mistake.
我错就错在让你留了这么长时间
My mistake was letting you stay around this long.
今天之内清空桌子
You got the day to pack your desk
办好文件交接
and pass off your files.
他在哪里
Where is he?
前面五个街区
Five blocks up ahead.
还在向北开
Still going northbound.
我没看到有越野车
I don't see an SUV.
等等  他们刚停车了
Hold up. They just pulled off.
我们看目标了
We got a visual.
-不要鸣警笛  -这里有很多人
- No sirens. - A lot of people here.
上车  上车
Get in your car. Get in your car.
蹲下  蹲下
Get down! Get down!
待在车里
Stay in your car!
上  上  上
Go. Go. Go.
没有司机
No driver!
看不清里面  不知是否安全
Can't see in. I can't clear this.
准备好了吗
Ready?
-举起手来  -举起手来
- Put your hands up. - Get 'em up! Up!
举起手来
Put your hands up!
让开门口
Get away from the door.
举着手  过来
Put 'em on your head. Come over.
他不在里面
He's not in there.
八爪在哪里
Where's Pulpo?
你以为结果会怎么样  琳娜
So how did you think this was gonna work out, Lina?
你们一家人可以逃跑
You guyse gonna leave
去南美过上幸福生活吗
and just be a big happy family in South America?
我想见我儿子
I want to see my son.
你告诉我们八爪去哪了
You tell us where Pulpo's headed,
你就可以见他
you can see him.
亚德勒斯让我租一辆车
Adres told me to rent a truck
5点的时候去第五街和普拉斯基街
and then pick him up at a taqueria
交叉路口的一个快餐店接他
at Fifth and Pulaski off the highway at 5:00.
还有什么
Anything else?
他说计划有变就给我打电话
He said if anything changed, he'd call me.
我们在她身上找到的一次性电话没有来电
The throwaway phone we found on her has zero calls.
八爪不会去第五街和普拉斯基街路口的
Pulpo ain't gonna be at Fifth and Pulaski.
他利用她和孩子来转移视线
He used her and the kid as diversion.
他故意让她被抓让我们失去线索
He wanted her to get caught to throw us off the scent.
把她交给重案组
Hey, just hand her over to major crimes,
通知儿童服务局带走她的孩子
and notify child services on her kid.
我们走
Let's go.
所有人都回头检查
Everyone go back and check
我们掌握的关于八爪的所有资料
every scrip of paper we have on Pulpo.
哪怕是他留在牢房里的午餐包装纸
I don't care if it's a jailhouse lunch wrapper
也不要放过
he left in the cage.
他所有的同伙  敌人
Every known associate, rival,
能查到的都仔细查
anything you can find.
事情变成这样我很遗憾
I'm sorry things didn't work out.
我没机会看这些文件了
I didn't get a chance to look at them, considering.
抓住这个家伙
Catch this guy.
为了安东尼奥
For Antonio.
阿特沃特  鲁塞克刚刚给我发了条短信
Hey, Atwater, I just got a text from Ruzek.
约你出去吗
You got a hot date?
不是  博伊特把萨姆纳给炒了
No. Voight gave Sumner the boot.
我擦
Damn.
他们会需要人顶替她
They're gonna need to replace her.
是啊
True.
我们俩都配得上这个位置对吗
Let's agree that we both deserve that spot.
当然
Bet.
好
Yeah.
伙计们  来看看这个
Hey, guys, check this out.
这是一份以亚德勒斯·迪亚斯的名义
It's a motion for assets petition
提交的资产清算动议
filed on behalf of Adres Dias.
有人想要保释八爪
Someone tried to bond Pulpo out.
他的保释金是一百万美元
His bond was set at 1 million dollars.
他没有被保释
He never made bail.
对  但是有人试过
Yeah, but somebody tried.
斯捷潘·内斯特诺夫
Stepan Nestrov
把他的夜总会作为资产列了进去
put his nightclub up as an asset,
但不值那么多钱
but it wasn't worth enough.
内斯特诺夫  俄罗斯人  过来
Nestrov--a Russian. Come here.
内斯特诺夫是埃斯顿街帮的成员
Nestrov's part of the Elston Ave Crew.
新入伙的俄罗斯人
Fresh-off-the-boat Russians
得替那些前辈干脏活
shipped over to do dirty work for the old-timers,
但他们决定自己单干
but they decided to break off on their own.
但是俄罗斯人痛恨哥伦比亚人
Yeah, and the Russians hate the Colombians.
那他们为什么想保释八爪呢
Then why'd they try to bond Pulpo out?
去那个俱乐部看看
Just get the address of that club.
警察  举起手来
Police! Hands up!
所有人把手举起来
Everybody, hands the air! Hands in the air!
举起手来  放在脑后
Put your hands behind your head!
后退
Back up!
别看我
Don't look at me.
-趴下  -趴在地上
- Get down! - Get down on the ground!
趴下  转过去
Get down! Turn around!
趴下  你也趴下
Get on the ground. Get down, you too.
趴在地上  双腿分开
Down on the ground. Spread your legs open.
5021紧急情况  有人对警察开枪
5021 emergency. Shots fired at the police.
嫌犯需要救护车
Suspect's gonna need an ambulance.
后面安全  我发现了更多可卡因
Back's clear. I see a lot more cocaine.
没有发现八爪
No Pulpo.
把手伸出来  张开双臂
Get your arms out. Spread 'em out. Spread 'em out.
把腿分开
Spread your legs.
为什么你要用你的俱乐部作抵押
So why would you put up your nightclub to bond out
保释一个谋杀罪在身的哥伦比亚毒枭
a Colombian drug lord who's wanted for murder, huh?
有人跟某人的妹妹在约会吗
Somebody dating somebody's sister?
你说什么
What was that?
你们从他的俱乐部没收的这台笔记本
Hey, you guys, this laptop you confiscated from his club,
我破解了密码
I cracked the password,
但是这些电子邮件我一封都看不懂
but I can't read any of the emails.
全是斯拉夫语
They're all in Cyrillic.
等我翻译出来恐怕黄花菜都凉了
It's gonna take me forever to translate this.
这下可好
Great.
值班警察不会刚好
I don't suppose we have a cop on shift
还有会俄语的吧
that reads Russian too.
我认识一个人
I know a guy.
看上去大部分都是他跟莫斯科的女朋友
So looks like most of these are back and forth
两个人之间的通信
to his girlfriend in Moscow.
等等
Uh, wait.
这里有一封是关于俄航货运的
Here's one about a shipment on Aeroflot.
-那是什么  -俄罗斯的一家航空公司
- What's that? - It's a Russian airline.
你觉得那是用来运可卡因的吗
You think it about shipping coke?
不知道  不过有一个附件
I don't know. There's an attachment, though.
是运输拖挂车的
Um, it's for a transport trailer.
运送几个运动包那么大的可卡因
You don't need a transport trailer
用不着运输拖挂车
to move a couple of gym bags of coke.
但如果运送越野车就用得着了
Yeah, but you do need one for SUVs.
这是一份通过俄航货机把两辆越野车
This is a bill of lading listing two vehicles
从[芝加哥]奥黑尔机场运到莫斯科的
being shipped on an Aeroflot cargo plane
提货清单
from O'hare to Moscow.
进来吧  布莱恩  没事
Come on in, Brian. It's all right.
过来
Come on.
问问他跟八爪是什么关系
Ask him what he's doing with Pulpo.
告诉他
Tell him--
跟他说如果他招了
Tell him if he talks,
我就从我们抓来的他的手下中找一个人
I'll charge one of his boys down in the cage
来担可卡因的事  他不会有事
with the cocaine, and he walks.
他问你是不是认真的
He asked if you're serious.
我的名声街知巷闻
He knows my reputation from the street.
我是个守信的人
I keep my word.
他说八爪鱼给了他们价值一百万的可卡因
He says the Octopus fronted them $1 million in cocaine.
所以他才帮他  他欠他的
That's why he's helping him. He owes him.
八爪在集装箱里吗
Is Pulpo in that container?
是的
Yes.
三点离开
It leaves at 3:00.
还有两个小时
That's in two hours.
谢谢
Thanks.
出什么问题了
What's the problem?
跟着我们  别紧张
Just follow us. Be cool.
下来
Come on down.
先把他带出去
Take him outside, and stay there.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开始吧
Let's go.
八爪  还记得我吗
Hey, Pulpo. Remember me?
你们可以走了
You can take off.
马上
Now.
好吧  那就这样了
Well, that's that, then.
带司机过来
Go get the driver.
好
Yeah.
干什么[西语]
Que haces?
别  等等
Come on. Wait!
干什么
What--
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
我会供出俄罗斯人的
I can give you the Russians.
也供出墨西哥人
I can give you the Mexicans.
别这样  老兄
Come on, man.
我才不管
I don't care.
别这样  老兄  逮捕我吧
Come on, man. Just arrest me, man!
来吧
Come on!
把我关进牢里吧  老兄
Take me to jail, man!
我也受够了
I'm tired!
还有一小时天就黑了
Be dark in an hour.
你还好吗
How you doing?
快渴死了
I'm dying of thirst.
我们抓到他了
We got him.
我没看到新闻里说
I didn't see it on the news.
不上新闻
I'm not sure you will.
过来
Come here.
杀了奥林斯基搭档的那个人
The guy who killed Olinsky's partner,
布朗宁
Browning--
他们应该把他带去了河滨路的码头
supposedly they took him to the docks on River Road.
带去干什么
And did what?
带他上船走一遭
Took him for a boat ride.
杰
Jay,
我想让八爪血债血偿
I want Pulpo punished for what he did,
但我这样我良心不安
but I don't want that on my conscience.
你呢
Do you?
似曾相识的感觉
Feels like deja vu.
没错  是有点
A little, yeah.
我一直不知道...
You know, I was never sure if um...
你杀布朗宁是因为埃迪
you killed Browning because of Eddie
还是因为想补偿你父亲
or because you were trying to make up for your father.
他杀了我们的搭档
He murdered our partner.
是
Yeah.
跟我父亲的事没有关系
What happened to my father had nothing to do with it.
布朗宁的事
Browning...
会让你夜不能寐吗
he ever keep you awake at night?
我睡得好得很
I sleep like a baby.
我已经二十年没睡过好觉了
Well, I haven't slept right in 20 years.
那不是因为我们杀了布朗宁
That's not 'cause we killed Browning.
是因为他杀了你的搭档
It's 'cause he killed your partner,
而你没有在场阻止
and you weren't there to stop it.
是的
Yep.
好吧  那我们从中学到什么教训没有
All right, so have we learned anything?
他肯定会老死狱中的
He's gonna die in prison.
我们不过帮是他一把
We're just speeding up the process.
来吧
Come on.
是时候了
It's time.
起来
Get up.
交给我
I got him.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你戴着芝加哥的大项链游过泳吗
You ever go swimming with a Chicago necklace?
不要
No!
别别别
Oh, no! no! no! no!
不要
No!
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
你去见过安东尼奥了
You went to see Antonio.
安东尼奥想的...
What Antonio wants...
和八爪应得的  可不是一回事
and what Pulpo deserves are two different things.
我们该把他带回局里
We need to turn him in.
此地今时
He dies right here...
就是他的死期
right now.
等等  等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait. Wait a second.
等等
Wait a second.
这小子说得对  我们抓住他  已经赢了
The kid's right, man. We got him. We won.
-埃尔文  -不是现在
- Alvin. - No, not now...
不是今晚
not tonight...
not tonight.
-交给你们了  -是的  警探
- You got him? - We got him, Detective.
走吧
Come on.
这些是所有的卷宗
All right, these are all the files right here.
谢谢
Thanks.
警长  你要见我们吗
Hey, Sarge, you wanted to see us?
对
Yeah.
你们可能听说我们现在有职位空缺了
You may have heard we have a spot open.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
我想立刻找人顶上
I want to fill it right away.
恭喜你  阿特沃特  欢迎加入情报组
Congratulations, Atwater. You just made Intelligence.
谢谢您  长官  非常感谢
Uh, thank you, sir. I appreciate that.
好了  明天来上班
All right, you start tomorrow.
-恭喜  凯文  -谢谢
- Congrats, Kevin. - Thank you.
-能等我一下吗  -没问题
- Would you give me a sec? - No doubt.
长官  我能问下为什么吗
Sir, can I ask why?
为什么不选你吗
You didn't make the cut?
你是个好警察  伯吉斯
You're good police, Burgess.
可是我不欣赏办公室恋情
I just don't tolerate in-house romance...
特别是对一个应该全力证明自己
Especially from a uniform who should be doing
能全身心投入工作的警员来说
everything she can to prove she's fully committed to the job.
-不是...  -你可以走了
- No, it's... - Dismissed.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
记得关门
Get the door.
你没事吧
Is everything all right?
怎么了
What happened?
我能进去吗
May I come in?
进来吧
Yeah.
很久没进来过了
It's been a while since I've been here.
安东尼奥的事...
You know, everything that happened to Antonio...
让我回想了很多埃迪的事
made me start thinking a lot about Eddie.
他被杀之后
After he was killed,
我故意疏远你
I put a lot of distance between me and you.
埃尔文  你还好吗
Alvin, are you okay?
我想修复我们关系
I want to make things right between us.
埃尔...
Al...
来
Hey, come here.
你迟到了
You're late.
我有点事耽搁了
I got caught up with something.
这是什么
And what is that?
我觉得这个很好
I thought it'd be nice.
适合五岁小孩
For a five-year-old.
特拉维斯都12岁了
Travis is 12.
我说过  你不能就这样
And I told you, you can't just invoke
突然有当爹的自觉了
your father-son privileges already.
小怀
Hey, T.
我给你介绍个人
I want you to meet somebody.
他是查理
This is Charlie.
我  他还有你妈妈  我们从小一块长大
Me and him and your mom, we all grew up together.
我们是老朋友了
We're old friends.
很高兴认识你  特拉维斯
Pleasure to meet you, Travis.
你喜欢熊队吗
You a Bears fan?
是啊
Yeah.
你最喜欢谁
Who's your favorite player?
厄拉赫
Urlacher.
他不错
That's a good choice.
但我喜欢老一辈的
But I'm old school.
辛格尔特里天下无敌
Can't beat Singletary.
你妈妈还是奇才粉吗
Your mom still a Packers fan?
别提了
Don't remind me.
早就料到了
Tell me about it.
好吧
Well, all right.
其实我只是来打个招呼
Well, I just wanted to stop by and say hey.
很久没见了
It's been a while.
很高兴你来  查理
I'm glad that you did, Charlie.
能谈谈吗
You got a sec?
好
Yeah.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
艾琳
Erin.
同不同意
Yes or no?
帮不帮我
Do you owe me?
你开玩笑的吧
Are you kidding?
你难道做好准备了吗
Do you have something cooking already?
别毁了这一切  查理
Don't blow this, Charlie.
同不同意
Yes or no?
你帮不帮我
Do you owe me?
当然帮
Yeah, sure.
很好
Good answer.
-再来杯曼哈顿  -好
- Let me have another Manhattan. - Sure.
他的都算我的
Whatever he's having.
-一样的来两杯  -好的
- Two of those. - You got it.
你先听我说
You're gonna hear me out first.
我注重的是当下
I deal with things in the moment.
我会尽力做最好的决定
I make the best decision that I can.
有时我是对的
Sometimes I'm right.
有时我是错的
Sometimes I'm wrong.
我都会接受
And I accept that,
然后我会向前看
and I move forward,
明白我为保护这座城市
knowing I did the best I can
尽了最大的努力
to protect this city.
我有自己的信条
I have my convictions,
我不在乎别人怎么想
and I don't give a damn what anybody thinks of 'em.
你也有自己的信条  杰
You have yours as well, Jay.
我知道
I know that.
我尊敬你的信条
And I respect that.
干杯
Cheers.
理查德·博伊特
祭奠逝者